blackdeserttome.com 2017-12-15

# BDO Tome - Error

At Critical Strike Solutions, LLC. we share your concerns about privacy. Accordingly we want you to understand what types of information we are collecting and what may happen to that information. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to our Terms of Use. Your use of our sites and any personal information you provide on the sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

### Collection of Information

Information is collected from our users at several different points during your visit. 

**Registration** : To use some resources available on our Site, a user may need to complete a registration process. During registration, a user is required to provide certain categories of information, which may include a name,address, e-mail address, and a password. 

**Optional Information:**  At various other points during your visit, you may be asked to provide information about yourself. For example, you may wish to participate in a survey or a contest. Participation in surveys or contests or the use of other services which require the input of additional information is completely voluntary on your part, and you have the choice about whether to disclose the information necessary to use these features of our site. 

**Passive Collection of Information:  **In addition to the information which you actively provide to us by methods such as completing the registration form, we collect information about how you interact with our site. We collect passive information for purposes such as testing and improving a user's experience at the site and the compilation of broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information for internal purposes and for disclosure to third parties such as advertisers and content partners. The types of passive information collected by this site include, without limitation, your IP address, which type of browser you are using, where you go on our site, and how long you stay on any part of our site. 

**Cookies:**  When you visit our sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Site may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

**Collection of Information from Children:  **We abide by federal law and the guidelines set up by the Federal Trade Commission regarding youth privacy (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). As such, we will not knowingly collect any personal information from or allow the registration of young people under the age of 13.

### Use of Information

We may use your information in order to customize our site to your interests and enhance your overall experience at our site. We try to recognize you using various methods, including having you log in with your user name and your password. Once we recognize you, pages, advertisements and other content may be customized for you so that you can see what interests you the most. In addition, as described above, we utilize passive information to learn more about how you interact with our site. This passive information may be combined with your other information for purposes such as testing and improving your experience at our site and the compilation of broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information for internal purposes and for disclosure to third parties such as advertisers and content partners. This aggregate passive information does not contain any personal information which can identify any individual user.

### Contacting You by Email

We may use your contact information periodically in order to send you e-mail regarding updates and to alert you or remind you of happenings on our sites. The frequency of these messages will vary depending upon various factors.

### Sharing of Information

We will not knowingly sell, share, rent or otherwise transfer your information other than in accordance with the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. We do not share any information that can be tied to you without your permission. If you give your permission to allow third parties to contact you, personal information about you (such as your contact information and other information collected during your visit) may be shared with builders, product manufacturers, data aggregators, marketers (possibly in the form of list rental), and other organizations. Regardless of your decision regarding the sharing of your personal information, we may share broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information with our business partners. This aggregate information does not contain any personal information which can identify any individual user. 

From time to time, we may decide that it is more efficient to use third parties to perform specific services, such as sending communications to our users. If we use a third party to provide specific services (such as sending communications to our users on our behalf), then information (such as contact information) may be shared with that party to the extent necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third party service providers are only allowed to use personally identifiable information for the purpose of providing the specific services requested by Critical Strike Solutions. The third party services covered by this paragraph do not include links to third party sites found on our site, which are governed by a more specific provision below. While we strive to protect the personal information of our users, we will release personal information if required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate.

### Security

We have security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and/or unauthorized alteration of the information under our control. You are the only user authorized to update your profile, unless you provide your password information to another party. We try to help protect personally identifiable information by utilizing both online and offline security methods, including firewalls, passwords and restricted physical access to the places where your information is stored. Our staff is trained to comply with our security procedures, and our security procedures are regularly reviewed and revised, if necessary, by the Privacy team at Critical Strike Solutions. 

If you have any questions about security issues at our site, please use our [contact form](http://www.blackdeserttome.com/contact) and we will try to answer your questions.

### Other Provisions

The Site is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

Your use of this site indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. 

In the event that we sell, assign or transfer some or all of its business to a successor or acquirer, we may sell, assign or transfer all of your information, regardless of your opt status, to such successor or acquirer. 

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we do not exercise control over the information, products, services or policies of third party companies accessible through our site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every third party site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected by this site. 

The State of CA enacted the Shine the Light law (CA Civil Code Sec 198.83) that permits users of our Site who are CA residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information during the past year for marketing purposes. To make such a request, you can use our [contact form](http://www.blackdeserttome.com/contact). 

Your privacy is important to us. If you have questions about any of the provisions described above, please contact us using our contact form.
